Guide to the Sophocles Papas papers, 1900-1998
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 1: 1987 Accession
  - Compositions pour la Guiter par Ferdinand Sor (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Ferdinand Sor Metod Completo para Guittarra (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Miscellaneous Sheet Music (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Compositions pour la Guiter par Ferdinand Sor (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Miscellaneous Sheet Music (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Ferdinand Sor - Miscellaneous Pieces (Box 20, Folder 35)
    Oversized
  - Guitar Transposer - Wheel - Nick Manoloff's Modern Accompaniment Guide (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Lyrics, Notes, Etc. (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Front and Back Covers (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Unknown Manuel, Incomplete (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Unknown Manuel, Part 3 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Technique Manuels (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Blank Composition Paper (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Text Manuscript - Guido Santorsola (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Text Manuscript - Guido Santorsola (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Home Study Course (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - John W. Schaum Theory Lessons, Book II (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Appointment Book, 1952 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Appointment Book, 1953 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Appointment Book, 1954 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Appointment Book, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Appointment Book, 1956 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Appointment Book, 1957 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Appointment Book, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Appointment Book, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Appointment Book, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Appointment Book, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Appointment Book, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Appointment Book, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Appointment Book, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Appointment Book, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Appointment Book, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Appointment Book, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Appointment Book, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Appointment Book, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Appointment Book, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Appointment Book, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Day at a Glance, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Day at a Glance, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Appointment Book, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Day at a Glance, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Engagements, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Telephone Address Book (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Framed Plaques and Award (Box 25)
  - Framed Plaques and Award (Box 26)
  - Records (Box 27)
  - Text Manuscripts, Oversize Transportation Wheel (Box 28)
  - Germany - Magazines (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Germany - Methods (Box 29, Folder 2-4)
  - US - Articles (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - US - Methods and Teaching Aids (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - US - Collections (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - US - Solos (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - US - Songs (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - US - Songs Printed in Greek (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Germany - Technical Studies (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Germany - Collections (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Germany - Solos (Box 30, Folder 3-4)
  - Germany - Songs (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Germany - Small Ensemble (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Brazil - Technical Studies (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Brazil - Collections (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Brazil - Solos (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Brazil - Songs (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Switzerland - Technical Studies (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Turkey - Duets (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Japan - Programs (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Japan - Magazines (Box 33, Folder 2-4)
  - Japan - Methods (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Japan - Collections I (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Japan - Collections II (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Japan - Solos (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Japan - Songs (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Belgium - Magazines (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Belgium - Technical Studies (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Belgium - Collections (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Belgium - Solos (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Belgium - Duets (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Hungary - Methods (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Hungary - Collections (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - England - Collections (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - England - Solos (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - England - Songs (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Netherlands - Magazines (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Netherlands - Technical Studies (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Netherlands - Solos (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Netherlands - Songs (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Sweden - Methods (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Sweden - Collections (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Greece - Methods (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Greece - Collections (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Greece - Solos (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Greece - Songs (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Greece - Orchestral (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Austria - Magazines (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Austria - Technical Studies (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Austria - Collections (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Austria - Solos (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Austria - Small Ensemble (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Italy - Magazines (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Italy - Methods (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Italy - Technical Studies (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Italy - Collections (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Italy - Solos (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Italy - Songs (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Spain - Magazines (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Spain - Methods (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Spain - Technical Studies (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Spain - Collections (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Spain - Solos (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - France - Magazines (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - France - Technical Studies (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - France - Collections (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - France - Solos (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - France - Songs (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Argentina - Magazines (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Argentina - Technical Studies (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Argentina - Collections (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Argentina - Solos (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Argentina - Songs (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Argentina - Incomplete and Unplaceable Music (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Duplicates (Box 38)
- Series 2: 1999 Accession
  This series contains music scores, instruction guides, guitar journals, and photographs included in the 1999 acquisition. Box numbers from the first acquisition repeat in this series.
  - Zequinha Abreu (Box 1, Folder 43)
    Tico-tico (Tico-tico no fuba)
  - Mario Abril (Box 2, Folder 35)
    Popular Music Classics for Classical Guitar
  - Adeste Fideles (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Dionisio Aguado (Box 19, Folder 30)
    Study
  - Dionisio Aguado (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Dionisio Aguado (Box 3, Folder 30)
    Walzer, Op. 3
  - Izaac Albinez (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Izaac Albinez (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Izaac Albinez (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Izaac Albinez (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Izaac Albinez (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Izaac Albinez (Box 20, Folder 9)
    Alborada
  - Mateo Albinez (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Album of Guitar Solos (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Laurindo Almeida (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - America (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Andres Segovia (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Andres Segovia (Box 16, Folder 31)
    Contributions to the World of Guitar
  - Anglica (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Appointment Books, 1951-1961 (Box 22)
  - Appointment Books, 1962-1971 (excluding 1968) (Box 23)
  - Appointment Books, 1974-1977, 1980 (Box 24)
  - Arabesque and Tsopanopoulo (Box 20, Folder 5)
    Compositions arranged by Sophocles Papas
  - Francisco Araujo (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Argentina - collections (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Argentina - pamphlets and newsletters (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Argentina - solos (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Argentina - songs (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Argentina - technical studies (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Eddia Arkin (Box 1, Folder 56)
    Classical Guitar Suite, "I'll sleep - when all debt is paid to the wind," "The caretaker of the hills," and "The swordsman's courage"
  - Nola Arndt (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Teach Yourself to Play the Guitar
  - Dave Arnold (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Jay Arnold, editor (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Articles (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Kathy Asp? (Box 18, Folder 5)
    Mood Espanol
  - Au Claire de la Lune (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Austria - collections (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Austria - journals, 1927, 1929-1930 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Austria - small ensemble (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Austria - solos (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Austria - technical studies (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Authentic Guitar Sounds of Peter, Paul and Mary (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Jose de Azpiazu (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - William Babell (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Johann Sebastian Bach (Box 1, Folder 61)
    Arioso, arranged by Laurindo Almeida
  - Johann Sebastian Bach (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Two Part Inventions for Piano
  - Johann Sebastian Bach (Box 18, Folder 5)
    Bouree
  - Johann Sebastian Bach (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Johann Sebastian Bach (Box 1, Folder 64)
    Gigue in E Major
  - Johann Sebastian Bach (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Johann Sebastian Bach (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Johann Sebastian Bach (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Johann Sebastian Bach (Box 10, Folder 07)
    Papas' Bach Album: 14 pieces by J. S. Bach for Guitar, arranged by Sophocles Papas
  - Johann Sebastian Bach (Box 1, Folder 60)
    Prelude from Cello Suite No. 1
  - Johann Sebastian Bach (Box 18, Folder 5)
    Prelude No. 1 (from The Well Tempered Clavichord - Book 1)
  - Johann Sebastian Bach (Box 8, Folder 19)
    Six pieces: Vol. II - 1. Prelude (Cello Suite No. 1), 2. Bist du bei mir, 3. Petite courante
  - Johann Sebastian Bach (Box 8, Folder 44)
    Sonata II: Vol. 1 - grave, fuga
  - Sonata II: Vol 2 - andante, allegro (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Fred J. Bacon (Box 20, Folder 6)
    Mia Amorita
  - F. Baldwin (Box 18, Folder 5)
    Merry Christmas to Mr. Papas in the Manner of Sor
  - M. W. Balfe (Box 2, Folder 13)
    Arranged by J. K. Mertz
  - Erno Balogh (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - The Band Played On (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Melchoir de Barberis (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Fantasia Terza
  - Agustin Barrios (Box 18, Folder 5)
    Las Abejas
  - Walter Kaye Bauer (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Mel Bay (Box 7, Folder 10)
    Buitar chords in photo diagram form
  - Mel Bay (Box 7, Folder 11-14)
    The Mel Bay Classic Guitar Method, Vols. 2-5
  - Mel Bay (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Mel Bay's Fun with the Mandolin
  - Ludwig van Beethoven (Box 1, Folder 44)
    Celebrated Minuet, arranged by Miguel Angel
  - Ludwig van Beethoven (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Ludwig van Beethoven (Box 19, Folder 30)
    Sonatine
  - Ludwig van Beethoven (Box 9, Folder 28)
    Two Short Pieces arranged by Sophocles Papas
  - Ludwig van Beethoven (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Ludwig van Beethoven (Box 19, Folder 30)
    Zwei Volksliedbearbeitungen
  - Belgium - collections (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Belgium - duets (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Belgium - journals, 1951-1952 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Belgium - solos (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Belgium - technical studies (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Believe Me If All Those Endearing Young Charms (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Arranged by William Foden
  - Leonard Bernstein and Stephen Sondheim (Box 3, Folder 19)
    West Side Story, arranged by Leon Block
  - Bicycle Built for Two (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Big Note Carnival (Box 4, Folder 22)
    Arranged by Maxwell Eckstein
  - Biographical Material (Box 17, Folder 1)
    book
  - Biographical Material (Box 17, Folder 2)
    clippings
  - Troy R. Bishop (Box 18, Folder 5)
    My Foolish Friend
  - Georges Bizet (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Seleccion de la opera "Carmen"
  - Carver Blanchard (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Karl Ludwig Blum (Box 19, Folder 30)
    Calmaiki; Tarantella, Op. 100
  - BMG: Banjo, Mandolin, Guitar (Box 16, Folder 1)
    Vol. XLVII, No. 542
  - BMG: Banjo, Mandolin, Guitar (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Vladimir Bobri (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Raul Borges (Box 8, Folder 15)
    Six Venezuelan Pieces: Vol. I, 1. Valse Venezolano, 2. Estudio, 3. Cancion de Cuna
  - Boston Classical Guitar Society Newsletter, November 1981 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Euday L. Bowman (Box 2, Folder 11)
    12th Street Rag
  - Johannes Brahms (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Brahms for the Guitar, arranged by Leon Block
  - Johannes Brahms (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Brazil - collections (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Brazil - solos (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Brazil - songs (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Brazil - technical studies (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - David Breaugh (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Brief biographies of noted guitarists (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Alfonso Broqua (Box 20, Folder 3)
    Evocaciones Criollas
  - Bulletin of the National Association for Music Therapy, Inc., Vol. VIII, No. 3, September 1959 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Bulletin of the Philharmonic Society of Guitarists, No. 23, May 1949 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Irving Bush (Box 2, Folder 33)
    Duet Sessions: Duets in the Modern Jazz Idiom
  - Charlie Byrd (Box 18, Folder 5)
    Prelude for Guitar
  - The Caissons Go Rolling Along (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - F. Calleja (Box 1, Folder 62)
    Cancion Triste, arranged by Carl van Feggelen
  - Campian (Box 18, Folder 5)
    Never Weather - Beaten Saile
  - Thomas Campion (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Suite
  - Matteo Carcassi (Box 7, Folder 17)
    Carcassi Classical Guitar Method, New Revised Edition
  - Matteo Carcassi, Melodious and Progressive Etudes for Guitar (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Matteo Carcassi (Box 2, Folder 23)
    12 Easy Pieces for the Guitar, Op. 10
  - Hoagy Charmichael and Parish Mitchell (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Star Dust
  - Ferdinando Carulli (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Ferdinando Carulli (Box 20, Folder 17)
    Abendmusik
  - Ferdinando Carulli (Box 10, Folder 10)
    Duet Etdue for Two Guitars
  - Ferdinando Carulli (Box 2, Folder 18)
    Fantasie Op. 323
  - Ferdinando Carulli (Box 20, Folder 14)
    Ouverture No. 1
  - Ferdinando Carulli (Box 20, Folder 11)
    Serenade No. 1
  - Ferdinando Carulli, Sonate No. 2 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Mario Castelnuovo-Tedesco (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Joseph Castle (Box 8, Folder 1)
    Guitar Workshop: A Practical Handbook for Beginning Guitarists
  - Harry Chalmers (Box 17, Folder 3)
    Wolf Patterns
  - Chicago Guitar Vol. 1, No. 16, June 1964 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Choice folk songs encores with guitar arrangements in American folk styles (Box 4, Folder 19)
    Arranged by Richard Cortland Harrison
  - Frederic Chopin (Box 10, Folder 8)
    Chopin Etude, arranged by Sophocles Papas
  - Frederic Chopin (Box 9, Folder 13)
    Three Preludes: Op. 28, Nos. 4, 6, 15
  - Frederic Chopin (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Two Preludes
  - A Christmas Recital for Piano (Box 2, Folder 28)
    Arranged by Maxwell Ekstein
  - Christmas with the King Family (Box 3, Folder 18)
    Arranged by John Lane
  - Domenico Cimarosa (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Al Citro (Box 18, Folder 5)
    Amazon
  - Mary Elizabeth Clark (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Classic American Folk Songs for Voice and Guitar (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Classic Guitar Editions (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - The Classic Guitar Journal (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Classic Guitar Recital Book (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Classic Melodies from the Great Composers for Piano for Beginners of All Ages (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Classic Melodies: Great Ballets for Piano for Beginners of All Ages (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Classical Guitar (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - The Classical Guitarist Vol. 4, No. 3, February 1968 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Muzio Clementi (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Clippings on Sophocles Papas (Box 38, Folder 24)
    Newspaper and magazine clippings
  - J. R. Colgan (Box 18, Folder 5)
    Three Preludes for Guitar
  - Columbia School of Music - miscellaneous (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Concert in Memory of Sophocles Papas (Box 38, Folder 26)
    Audio cassette
  - Arcangelo Gavotta (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Corelli, arranged by George Warren
  - Correspondence, 1966-1983 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence (Box 38, Folder 16)
    Greek language with some translations
  - Correspondence (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Napoleon Coste (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Napoleon Coste (Box 19, Folder 30)
    Barcarolle
  - Napoleon Coste (Box 19, Folder 30)
    Rondeau
  - Alfred Cottin (Box 1, Folder 75)
    Les premiers pas
  - Country Gardens (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Francois Couperin (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Herrlee Creel (Box 38, Folder 10)
    Guitar Therapy
  - Dance of the shadows, from "Dinorah" (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Danza (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Evelyn Danzig and Jack Segal (Box 1, Folder 45)
    Scarlet Ribbons (for her hair)
  - Alfred D'Auberge and Morton Manus (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Charles De Beriot (Box 3, Folder 26)
    Three Duos concertants for Two Violins
  - Claude Debussy (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Clair de Lune
  - Claude Debussy (Box 18, Folder 4)
    La fille aux cheveux de lin
  - Leonhard de Call (Box 20, Folder 15)
    Nr 27/28 quartett fur 4 gitarren
  - Descriptive checklist of selected manuscripts in the monasteries of Mount Athos (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Robert DeVisee (Box 19, Folder 30)
    Bourree; Menuet
  - Robert DeVisee (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Robert DeVisee (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Robert DeVisee (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Anton Diabelli (Box 19, Folder 30)
    Barre study
  - Anton Diabelli (Box 19, Folder 30)
    Guitarre
  - Anton Diabelli (Box 20, Folder 10)
    Sontaine
  - Nathanael Diesel (Box 1, Folder 52)
    Suite in G Major
  - Gene Dixon (Box 1, Folder 14)
    There's a Sweetheart in Nebraska
  - James L. Dixon (Box 1, Folder 13)
    The District of Columbia is my home town
  - Wojciech Dlugoraj (Box 19, Folder 30)
    Villanella
  - Alan Dodd (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Alan Dodd (Box 1, Folder 37)
    Rue de blue (Bossa Nova)
  - "Doina": Romanian folk ballet of Bucharest (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - D. C. Dounis (Box 8, Folder 6)
    Fundamental trill studies on a scientific basis for violin
  - D. C. Dounis (Box 5, Folder 4)
    The higher development of thirds and fingered octaves: twenty-four advanced formulas for the violin, Op. 30
  - John Dowland (Box 19, Folder 30)
    Alman
  - John Dowland (Box 20, Folder 20)
    Altenglische madrigale zur laute
  - John Dowland (Box 18, Folder 5)
    As I wente to Walsinghame; Almane; Tarletone Riserrectione; Mistris Whitte's thinge
  - John Dowland (Box 18, Folder 5)
    Dos gallardas
  - John Dowland (Box 1, Folder 74)
    Earl of Essex, his galliard, and the sick tune; arranged by Mitsuhiko Hamada
  - Drink to my only with thine eyes (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - John W. Duarte (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - John W. Duarte (Box 19, Folder 30)
    Prelude No. 1, Op. 13
  - John W. Duarte (Box 8, Folder 34)
    Simple variations of "Las Folias"
  - Charles Duncan (Box 7, Folder 20)
    The art of classical guitar playing
  - Antonin Dvorak (Box 19, Folder 30)
    Largo
  - George C. Economides (Box 8, Folder 7)
    The study of the guitar simplified
  - Editions Orphee: preliminary catalogue (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Ruth Edwards and Eric Simon (Box 6, Folder 1)
    First steps in music: a new approach to music for beginners of all ages
  - El noy de la mare (Box 1, Folder 79)
    Arranged by Carl van Feggelen
  - El noy de la mare (Box 9, Folder 25)
    Arranged by Sophocles Papas
  - England - collections (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - England - solos (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Wayne Erbsen (Box 5, Folder 20)
    Complete and painless guide to the guitar for young beginners
  - Joseph M. Estella (Box 2, Folder 27)
    Guitar songtime: solos, duets, groups, singing
  - Joseph M. Estella (Box 7, Folder 3)
    Smith's how to play finger picking style guitar
  - Estudio poetico (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Etude: the music magazine Vol. 73, Nos. 11-12, Vol. 74, No. 1, 1955-1956 (Box 13, Folder 12-14)
  - European guitar and lute music: Book two - German masters (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Marvin Falcon (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Marvin Falcon (Box 9, Folder 39)
    Greek dance and lament
  - Fantasia di Francesco Milanese (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Joe Fava (Box 7, Folder 18)
    Method for guitar - Book 2
  - Favorite collection of Hawaiian guitar solos (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Jose Ferrer (Box 10, Folder 11)
    Spanish favorites for classic guitar
  - Fifty Greek dances (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - FIGA news, May 1969 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    Incomplete
  - First duet album for two violins (Box 3, Folder 14)
    Arranged by Harvey S. Whistler and Herman A. Hummel
  - First etude album for violin (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - First quartet album for three violins (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - First trio album for three violins (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Johann K. Fischer (Box 18, Folder 5)
    Minuet
  - Five Catalan melodies (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Five solos for guitar (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Five solos for the Hawaiian guitar (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - William Foden (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Listen to the mocking bird
  - William Foden (Box 10, Folder 9)
    Six short preludes (chord progressions)
  - Folk Tunes for solo descant recorder (Box 4, Folder 21)
    Arranged by T. S. Walker
  - The folk song sight singing series, Book VIII (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Folk song sing along (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Carlos Alberto P. Fonseca (Box 8, Folder 26)
    Seven Brazilian etudes
  - Stephen Foster (Box 9, Folder 23)
    Jeannie with the light brown hair
  - Stephen Foster (Box 19, Folder 30)
    Oh! Suzanna, Massa's in the cold cold ground, My old Kentucky home
  - Framed plaques and awards (Box 25)
  - Framed plaques and awards (Box 26)
  - France - collections (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - France - journals (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - France - solos (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - France - songs (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - France - technical studies (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Cesar Franck (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Symphonic skeleton scores: No. 3 - Franck symphony in D minor
  - R. E. Franklin (Box 18, Folder 5)
    A blues for guitar
  - Ay Ay Ay (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Arranged by Walter Kaye Bauer
  - The French funny book of popular tunes in easy piano arrangements (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Fretts: news fromt he fretted instrument world, June/July 1958, Feb/Mar, June/July, July/Aug 1959, 1960, 1962, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 26-32)
  - Signor Friscoe and H. Quali Clark (Box 3, Folder 17)
    Shake it and break it, arranged by Harry Volpe and Frank Victor
  - Bernice Frost (Box 7, Folder 9)
    At the piano: Book for two class or individual instruction based on folk tunes of many countries and themes from the masterpieces of music
  - Gagliarda (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - V. Galileo (Box 18, Folder 5)
    Saltarello
  - Patricio Galindo (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Jose Galles (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Sonata in E minor
  - Louis Garrow (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Boogie and blues for piano solo
  - Donald Garwood (Box 6, Folder 8)
    Masters of instrumental blues guitar
  - Gautier (Box 1, Folder 70)
    8 courantes in Renaissance tuning
  - Geordie (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Germany - collections (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Germany - journals and newsletters, 1952-1960, 1962-1963, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 06)
  - Germany - methods (Box 31, Folder 7-8)
  - Germany - methods (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Germany - miscellaneous (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Germany - small ensemble (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Germany - solos (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Germany - solos (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Germany - songs (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Germany - technical studies (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - R. Gernlein (Box 19, Folder 30)
    Thema, Op. 42
  - Giardini (Box 19, Folder 30)
    Come thou almighty King
  - Gibson system for guitar, part 3 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Giga meloncolica (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Gigue (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Gilbert and Sullivan (Box 3, Folder 29)
    The Mikado, arranged by William Krevit
  - Mauro Giuliani (Box 19, Folder 30)
    Allegro vivace, Op. 8; Allegro vivace, Op. 40, No. 23; Jagdstuck (rondo), Op. 30; Menuetto, Op. 20; Thema, Op. 34; Walzer, Op. 57, No. 3
  - Mauro Giuliani (Box 18, Folder 5)
    Grande ouverture pour la guitare
  - Mauro Giuliani (Box 19, Folder 30)
    Grazioso
  - Mauro Giuliani (Box 5, Folder 6)
    120 daily guitar studies for the right hand
  - Mauro Giuliani (Box 20, Folder 19)
    Serenade concertante en trio pour guitare, violon et violoncello
  - Mauro Giuliani (Box 18, Folder 5)
    Sonata, Op. 15
  - God rest ye merry gentlemen (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Arranged by Joe Hagerty
  - The golden age: classics for solo guitar - Book one (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Graded anthology for classic guitar (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Enrique Granados (Box 19, Folder 30)
    Danza Espanola No. 5